所以为了准备这个申请，我们从第一步开始，
So to prepare the application,
cuz we're starting at step one,
我们谈谈你的简历吧
let's talk about your resume.
恩，杰姆，这是前端面试课程，为什么我们还不做问题呢 ?
Yeah, Jem, this is front-end interviewing
course, why aren't we doing problems yet?
再一次，你必须先到那里才能解决这些问题。
Again, you gotta get in there first
before you can solve these problems.
所以你的简历应该是一页
So your resume should be one page.
除非你是个我不知道的诺贝尔奖得主
Unless you're a, I don't know,
accomplished Nobel laureate and
你的名字有 20 项专利甚至 20 项专利
you've got 20 patents to your name,
even 20 patents,
你大概可以把它切成五个，五个好的。
you can probably cut that down to 5,
the 5 good ones.
但你需要一个页面，因为作为招聘经理或者招聘人员
But you want one page, because as
a hiring manager or a recruiter you're
成千上万的简历和数以千计的简历
looking at thousands of resumes, thousands
and thousands and thousands of resumes.
所以你想速速地说
So you want it quick and to the point.
你想列出你的技能你想列出你的经验
You wanna list your skills,
you wanna list your experience,
你工作的公司
the companies you've worked at.
你想看看你的样子他们想知道你的技术很熟悉
You wanna look at your, they wanna
see your technology familiarity,
你和你一起做了什么
what sort of stacks have you worked with?
他们可能想看你的教育
They might wanna see your education.
有些公司在计算机科学学位上对 CS 有硬性规定，
Some companies have a hard requirement
on CS, on a computer science degree,
有些公司不知道
some companies don't.
就是我们可以做一个其他的课程你需要一个 CS 学位
That is, we could do a whole other
course on do you need a CS degree for
前期工程，还是工程 ?
front-end engineering, or any engineering?
不同的时间，不同的地方。
Different time, different place.
但有些人想知道你的教育或者你去的任何训练营
But some people wanna know your education,
or any boot camps you went to,
任何你的认证
any sort of certifications you have.
他们想知道你的成就
They wanna know your accomplishments,
and that's it.
你可以很喜欢这就是我简历的片段
You can gussy this up,
this is a snippet of my resume.
所以我没骗你如果我申请工作就是我要送的
So I'm not lying to you, if I was applying
for a job this is what I'd send out.
但那就别多想了
But that's it,
don't overthink it too much,
不要花太多的时间让它变得和图形和所有这些都是一样的
don't spend too much time making it
pretty with graphics and all that.
如果你想的话我不会告诉你该怎么做
You can if you want,
I'm not gonna tell you what to do.
事实上我要告诉你该怎么做别这么做
Actually, I am gonna tell you what to do,
don't do that.
花你的时间去满足
Spend your time getting to
the core requirements of what
有人在找
someone's looking for.
所以记住，想想同情，想想，谁想雇用我或者
So remember, think empathy, think, what
is the person who is trying to hire me or
雇佣你的工程师他们要看什么
hire your engineers,
what are they gonna look at?
如果你要做 1000 次你想看什么
And if you had to do that 1,000 times,
what do you wanna see,
怎么会很快地向你跳呢
what's gonna jump out
to you really quickly?